Neveh Allon

Web Developer

Focused Full-stack Developmer. Aiming to leverage proven problem-solving, research, and language skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

NevehAllon@gmail.com

1 (267)-631-2969 535-5320

052-

Jerusalem

Israel

Chicago, USA Jerusalem, Israel

nevehallon.github.io/portfolio_2 021

in

linkedin.com/in/neveh-allon

github.com/nevehallon



stackoverflow.com/users/93567 33/neveh

SKILLS

Angular TypeScript

React.js Node.js

Material Bootstrap

JQuery SASS

NoSQL Docker

Wordpress

Google Cloud

PHP

Figma

JQuery python

MongoDB

Adobe Creative Suite

EDUCATION

Full-stack Web Development

HackerU

10/2019 - 06/2021

Front-End Developer Nanodegree

Google/Udacity

11/2017 - 08/2018

Front End Development Program, Computer Software

freeCodeCamp

09/2017 - 02/2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Development

independant

05/2020 - present

Tasks

 Discussing requirements with clients, making website development proposals, designing page layout, working with content management systems, making sure work follows the client's vision, writing code, implimenting graphic design.

Firewood processor and distributor

Tekoa Firewood

04/2015 - present

Tasks

- Splitting, handling and bundling firewood, operating equipment
- Operating as part of a team
- moving/sorting, loading and unloading firewood for delivery

Armed Security Officer

Tekoa Security

06/2016 - 05/2017

Tasks Maintained constant state of overall security in a gated community

MILITARY SERVICE

IDF (03/2012 - 03/2015)

Military Police Detective, Company Educations and Training Logistics NCO, Company Communications and Logistics NCO, Combat Commander

CERTIFICATES

Google/Udacity: Front-End Developer Nanodegree (11/2017 - 08/2018)

freeCodeCamp Certificit of completion - Front End Development Program, Computer Software (09/2017 - 02/2018)

Full-stack Web Development at HackerU

WORK PORTFOLIOS

https://nevehallon.github.io/portfolio_2021

https://nevehallon.github.io/my-app (2018)

LANGUAGES

English

Native / Bilingual Proficiency

Hebrew

Native / Bilingual Proficiency